# **Subin Kim**

Homepage: https://subin-kim-cv.github.io GitHub: https://github.com/subin-kim-cv

Email: subin-kim@kaist.ac.kr

RESEARCH **INTERESTS**  The long-term goal of my research is to enhance the practicality of computer vision systems so that they can be widely used in real-world scenarios. To this end, I focus on (i) how to design architecture efficiently in terms of memory and computation by reflecting the character of each data signal and (ii) how to apply computer vision systems newly and variously in real-world applications.

Currently, my research interest lies in representing complex data signals efficiently by utilizing coordinatebased neural representations and mainly working on a dynamic 3D video synthesis.

**Keywords**: Implicit neural representation, Neural rendering, Generative modeling

**EDUCATION** 

# M.S. in Artificial Intelligence

Mar. 2022 - Present

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST), Daejeon, Korea

Advisor: Prof. Jinwoo Shin

# **B.S.** in Electrical Engineering

Mar. 2017 - Feb. 2022

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST), Daejeon, Korea

Magna Cum Laude (GPA: 3.93/4.3)

#### **Conferences**

[1] Scalable Neural Video Representations with Learnable Positional Feature Subin Kim\*, Sihyun Yu\*, Jaeho Lee, Jinwoo Shin

Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS) 2022

**EXPERIENCE** 

WORK

### **External Collaborator**

Oct. 2022 - Present

Adobe, San jose, USA (remote)

with Joon-young Lee

**External Collaborator** Mar. 2022 - Present

POSTECH, Pohang, Korea (remote)

with Prof. Jaeho Lee

**AI Research Intern** Aug. 2021 - Feb. 2022

Upstage, Yongin, Korea (remote)

with Sungrae Park

**Undergraduate Research Intern** Feb. 2021 - Feb. 2022

KAIST, Daejeon, Korea with Prof. Jinwoo Shin

Jan. 2020 - Feb. 2020 **Winter Internship** 

Samsung Electro-Mechanics, Suwon, Korea

**HONORS** Travel Award, NeurIPS 2022

First Place, Creative Space G A.I & IoT Hackathon

PUBLICATIONS \* denotes equal contribution

INVITED	"Scalable Neural Video Representations with Learnable Positional Features"	Nov. 2022
TALKS	NeurIPS 2022 at KAIST	
	"Scalable Neural Video Representations with Learnable Positional Features"  Samsung Advanced Institute of Technology (Remote)	Nov. 2022
	"Scalable Neural Video Representations with Learnable Positional Features"	Jun. 2022
	Rokit Healthcare (Seoul, Korea)	

#### **PROJECTS**

## **Emotion-based Video-conferencing Application for Enhanced Interactions** Mar. 2020 - Jun. 2020

- Developed EVA, an emotion-based video conferencing application designed to make the video conference more enjoyable and interactive; utilized deep learning-based techniques to enable EVA: (i) detect the faces of the participants and (ii) recognize their real-time emotions.
- One can apply 3D face masks on the faces shown in applications and interact with other users using the emoji features based on the detected emotions of each of them.
- Also, EVA analyzes the facial expressions of all participants in order to give the presenter an indication of how the audience is feeling, as well as to find participants who are sleeping.

#### REFERENCE

Prof. Jinwoo Shin, Graduate School of AI & School of Electrical Engineering, KAIST

Contact: jinwoos@kaist.ac.kr

Prof. Jaeho Lee, Department of Electrical Engineering & Graduate School of AI, POSTECH

Contact: jaeho.lee@postech.ac.kr